== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Leonard:)Look at all these activities
the university has.
(Leonard:)Rock climbing club,
archery, flag football.
(Sheldon:)Had me at flag,
lost me at football.
(Penny:)Yeah, I think it's great you
guys want to get more exercise,
(Penny:)but do you really think sports
is the right choice for you?
(Leonard:)What are you saying?
We're not coordinated enough
(Leonard:)to play sports?
(Penny:)Okay, Leonard, sweetheart,
(Penny:)you twisted your ankle
playing Scrabble.
(Leonard:)I got a triple-word score
with a double letter "Q."
If that's not a time
to bust out the Scrabble dance,
what's the point of having one?
(Leonard:)Hey, Barry Kripke
started a fencing club.
(Sheldon:)Interesting. Sword fighting does
hold a certain elegant appeal.
(Sheldon:)And I would imagine
it meets many
(Sheldon:)of our personal criteria
for a sport.
(Leonard:)It's indoors, so no sunscreen.
(Sheldon:)No throwing, no catching,
(Sheldon:)no running.
(Leonard:)No gym shorts
that can be yanked down.
(Sheldon:)Or worse, up.